[{"answer": "Well, certainly, I expected the book to make quite a big splash.", "docId": "111031pmt", "aSentId": 26, "question": "How do you think that the interviews you've done so far and the published tell-all book is all going down?", "qSentId": 25}, {"answer": "Well, I understand that completely.", "docId": "111031pmt", "aSentId": 33, "question": "What do you say to that?", "qSentId": 32}, {"answer": "Well, the mission is to have the ability to tell our story in our own words, and to be able to broker a reconciliation between Andrew and his mother, and also to offer a story about our lives that hopefully tells many people that you can have a healing experience through telling your own story.", "docId": "111031pmt", "aSentId": 49, "question": "And what was the mission?", "qSentId": 48}, {"answer": "I don't feel that Catherine and Andrew have been hiding anything.", "docId": "111031pmt", "aSentId": 55, "question": "Is it easier to say Andrew has, as some people say, $60 million, and then -- and then when people have that picture in their head of that sum of money, they can assess whether they believe it is ethically and morally right for you guys to profit -- or Catherine in particular, to personally profit further from telling the story of Bernie Madoff's crimes?", "qSentId": 54}, {"answer": "I mean, this is -- I think --", "docId": "111031pmt", "aSentId": 61, "question": "If it's so -- if it is not a secret and they're so open and public and everyone appears to know apart from me, why don't you just tell me?", "qSentId": 60}, {"answer": "Well, the money that Andrew earned in his career is what represents his net worth and that's what he's being sued for.", "docId": "111031pmt", "aSentId": 70, "question": "In other words, how much money came from the Ponzi scheme to be invested or be used in Andrew's apparently legitimate end of the business?", "qSentId": 69}, {"answer": "I cannot imagine that he would.", "docId": "111031pmt", "aSentId": 118, "question": "Do you think he is resolute now that he will never talk to him again?", "qSentId": 117}, {"answer": "I believe that life begins at conception.", "docId": "111031pmt", "aSentId": 142, "question": "What's your view of abortion?", "qSentId": 141}, {"answer": "No circumstances.", "docId": "111031pmt", "aSentId": 146, "question": "No circumstances?", "qSentId": 145}, {"answer": "You're mixing two things here, Piers.", "docId": "111031pmt", "aSentId": 160, "question": "If one of your female children, grandchildren was raped, you would honestly want her to bring up that baby as her own?", "qSentId": 159}, {"answer": "You're mixing two things here.", "docId": "111031pmt", "aSentId": 162, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 161}, {"answer": "Yeah, don't tell me that.", "docId": "111031pmt", "aSentId": 706, "question": "It's on the rocks?", "qSentId": 705}, {"answer": "Yes, as far as I know.", "docId": "111031pmt", "aSentId": 712, "question": "Still happily marry?", "qSentId": 711}]